youngsterchoice.com 2018-03-17

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policies For youngsterchoice.com

We find that privacy of your personal information is  vital. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit **http://www.youngsterchoice.com** and how we  protect your information.

### Personal Identification Information

We may collect personal information identification information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to when users visits our site or respond to a survey and in connection with other activities, services, features and resources we make available on our site. User may be asked for appropriate name, email address, phone number. We will collect Personal Identification Information from users only if they submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply Personal Identification Information as it is optional in some cases .

### Non Personal Identification Information

We may collect non Personal Identification Information about users whenever they interact with our website. Non Personal Identification Information may include the browser name such as google chrome, the type of computer whether it is  window based or something else.

### Web Browse Cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to  order to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### How we use collect Information

**youngsterchoice.com**  collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes which are listed below:

– To personalize user experience

we may use information in order to gathered the information whether a user satisfies or not.

– To improve our Site

we may use information to improve our site performance and to make our site reliable.

– To improve customer service

your information helps us to more effectively and reliability respond to your customer service .

### How we protect your information

We  use appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site and this information is saved to our database and it is not used as to globally access to any unauthorized access.

### Google Ad-sense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the dart cookies enables it to serve ads to user based on their visit to our site and other sites on the internet.

### Compliance With Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially vital. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13 as  the  name of the site implies that this website is particularly helpful for the youngsters of our country

### Changes to the Privacy Polices

**youngsterchoice.com** has the right to update this privacy policy at any time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent.

### Your Acceptance of these terms

You  must signify your acceptance of this policy.by using this website. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site because it is the responsibility of the user to agree to the terms and conditions  as suggested by the admin.

**Contact us**

If you have any question regarding our website then you can contact us at **samaksharora@youngsterchoice.com**
